Guide to the Consumer Reports. Editorial Department records, 1934-2015, bulk 1936-1997 RL.11863
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Consumer Reports. Editorial Department records
1934-2015, bulk 1936-1997
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Consumer Reports (Firm)
RL.11863
30.0 Linear Feet
Consumer Reports is a product testing and consumer advocacy nonprofit organization based in Yonkers, N.Y., founded in 1936. The Editorial Department is responsible for the production of the organization's serial publications and promotional literature. The Editorial Department records include biographical information, corporate anniversary planning documents, correspondence, publication drafts, research and investigative materials, texts of speeches and testimonies, and other printed materials. The collection also contains office files of several Editors and departmental directors, including Dexter Masters, Donal Dinwiddie, and Mildred Brady. Acquired as part of the John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History.
Arrangement
Organized into the following series: Administrative Files; Consultants; Directors and Editors; Publication Production Files.
Biographical / Historical
Consumer Reports is a product testing and consumer advocacy nonprofit organization based in Yonkers, N.Y., founded in 1936. The Editorial Department is responsible for the production of the organization's serial publications and promotional literature.
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Provenance
The Consumer Reports. Editorial Department records were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift in 2019.
Related Materials
Related materials may be found in the following Hartman Center collections:
Consumer Reports Archives records
Consumer Reports Books records
Consumer Reports. Board of Directors records
Consumer Reports. Colston E. Warne papers
Collection Overview
The Editorial Department records include biographical information, corporate anniversary planning documents, correspondence, publication drafts, research and investigative materials, texts of speeches and testimonies, and other printed materials. The collection also contains office files of several Editors and departmental directors, including Dexter Masters, Donal Dinwiddie, and Mildred Brady.
Consumer advocacy; Consumer education; consumer protection; Publishers and publishing -- History; John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History
- Administrative Files, 1938-1986; 1
  - Office Files, 1938-1980; 1
    - Circulation, U.S. Post Office, 1957-1975; 2 folders (Box 1)
    - Consumer Reports bound volumes correspondence, 1951-1971 (Box 1)
    - Consumer Reports indexing, 1970-1973 (Box 1)
    - Consumers Union policy memos, 1968; 1979 (Box 1)
    - Consumers Union style book, 1938-1980 (Box 1)
    - Microfilming royalties, 1977 (Box 1)
    - Microfilming royalties, 1977 (Box 48)
    - Movie reviewsd opinion post cards, 1949 (Box 1)
    - Publications reviewed in Consumer Reports by John Brooks, 1963-1964 (Box 1)
  - Consumers Union Anniversaries, 1961-1986; 2
    - 25th anniversary idea book, 1961; 3 folders (Box 1)
    - 30th anniversary--Correspondence and publicity planning, 1964-1966; 2 folders (Box 2)
    - 30th anniversary--Dexter Masters book, 1966; 6 folders (Box 2)
      Scope and Contents
      The Intelligent Buyer's Guide to Sellers: A Moral Reader in Three Parts
    - 35th anniversary--Brochure, 1971; 3 folders (Box 2)
    - 35th anniversary--Brochure, 1971; 2 folders (Box 3)
    - 35th anniversary--Brochure, 1971 (Box 48)
    - 35th anniversary--Brochure, 1971 (Box 50)
    - 35th anniversary--Colston Warne letter, 1971 (Box 3)
    - 35th anniversary--Planning, 1971 (Box 3)
    - 40th anniversary--Planning, 1976 (Box 3)
    - 50th anniversary--50 Years Ago, 1985-1986; 3 folders (Box 3)
    - 50th anniversary--50 Years Ago, 1985-1986 (Box 48)
    - 50th anniversary--50 Years of Testing, 1986 (Box 3)
    - 50th anniversary--50 Years of Testing, 1986 (Box 4)
    - 50th anniversary--Conference on poverty, 1986 (Box 4)
    - 50th anniversary--Memo to members, 1986 (Box 4)
    - 50th anniversary--On Display: 50 Years of Goods and Services (Once Over), 1986; 3 folders (Box 4)
- Consultants, 1934-1988; 2015; 2
  - Correspondence, 1946-1975; 5 folders (Box 4)
  - Correspondence--Economic conditions, 1952-1958 (Box 5)
  - Correspondence--Editorial consultants, 1963-1975 (Box 5)
  - Cresap McCormick & Paget--Evaluation of Location Alternatives, 1971 (Box 5)
  - Harold Aaron (medical advisor), 1940-1988; 2 folders (Box 5)
  - Harold Webber (automotive safety), 1959 (Box 5)
  - John Dorfman (economics advisor), 1974 (Box 5)
  - Marvin Lipman (medical advisor), 1968-1975 (Box 5)
  - Mildred Brady (special editorial advisor), 1958-1960 (Box 5)
  - Robert Brady, 1934-1942 (Box 5)
  - Robert Brady--Book material, 1954; 2 folders (Box 5)
  - Robert Brady--Brady Report, 1956 (Box 6)
  - Robert Brady--Correspondence, 1938-1956; 2 folders (Box 6)
  - Robert Brady--Obituary and eulogy, 1963 (Box 6)
  - Robert Brady--Planning and Technology, 1950 (Box 6)
  - Robert Brady--Planning of Production in an Industrial System, 1950 (Box 6)
  - Ruth and Edward Brecher, 1948-1974; 2015 (Box 6)
- Directors and Editors, 1936-1997; 3
  - David Maness, 1959; 3
    - Correspondence, 1959 (Box 6)
  - Dexter Masters, 1940; 4
    - Correspondence, 1940 (Box 6)
  - Donal Dinwiddie, 1956-1977; 5
    - Auto quarterly proposal, 1971 (Box 7)
    - Board reports, 1967-1971 (Box 7)
    - Consultants, 1965-1969 (Box 7)
    - Consumer journalism conference, 1971 (Box 7)
    - Con$umer New$week, 1972 (Box 7)
    - Consumers Union fellowship (William Wilt), 1970 (Box 7)
    - Consumers Union policy, 1956-1972 (Box 7)
    - Correspondence and memoranda, 1965-1973; 11 folders (Box 7)
    - Correspondence--Channing Lushbough, 1971-1973 (Box 8)
    - Correspondence--Gilbert Thelan (Washington Editor), 1972-1973 (Box 8)
    - Correspondence--Gordon Hyatt (Broadcast/Film), 1973 (Box 8)
    - Correspondence--Henry Villard (Board member), 1966-1972; 2 folders (Box 8)
    - Correspondence--Interoffice memos, 1966-1973; 2 folders (Box 8)
    - Correspondence--Ira Furman (Public Information Department), 1970-1973 (Box 8)
    - Correspondence--John Hanc (Market Services), 1968-1973 (Box 8)
    - Correspondence--Jonathan Leff (Consumer Reports Books), 1967-1973 (Box 8)
    - Correspondence--Marvin Lipman (medical consultant), 1968-1973 (Box 8)
    - Correspondence--Monte Florman (Technical Department), 1966-1973 (Box 8)
    - Correspondence--Paul Goldberg (Promotion Department), 1968-1972 (Box 8)
    - Correspondence--Paul Kellam (Managing Director), 1971-1973 (Box 8)
    - Correspondence--Robert L. Smith (Assistant Director), 1968-1970 (Box 8)
    - Correspondence--Robin Lanier (Assistant Editor), 1966-1969 (Box 8)
    - Correspondence--Sidney Shainwald (Accounting), 1969-1973 (Box 8)
    - Correspondence--Survey Unit, 1970-1973 (Box 8)
    - Correspondence--Walker Sanbach (Executive Director), 1966-1973; 2 folders (Box 9)
    - Editorial content, 1964-1973 (Box 9)
    - Editorial Research Unit, 1967 (Box 9)
    - Encyclopedia project, 1970-1971 (Box 9)
    - Encyclopedia project--Master list of entries, 1970-1971 (Box 9)
    - Encyclopedia project--Memos--Caryn Leland, 1971 (Box 9)
    - Encyclopedia project--Sample Preparation: Food and Beverages, 1971 (Box 9)
    - Home buying series (Jim Blakely, not published), 1972-1973 (Box 9)
    - Home buying series (Jim Blakely, not published), 1972-1973 (Box 48)
    - Housing article, 1970-1971 (Box 9)
    - Housing article, 1970-1973; 3 folders (Box 10)
    - Long Range Plan Committee, 1970-1971; 2 folders (Box 10)
    - Management Committee, 1969-1972 (Box 10)
    - Management Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 11)
    - Management Staff Memo, 1972-1973; 2 folders (Box 11)
    - Operations Committee, 1966-1973; 4 folders (Box 11)
    - Operations Committee, 1972 (Box 45)
    - Policy on legal checking (C.T. Corporation article), 1971-1972 (Box 12)
    - Press Galleries--Consumers Union exclusion, 1973 (Box 12)
    - Search committee for Executive Director, 1973 (Box 12)
    - Speeches, 1968-1970 (Box 12)
    - Study--Business and consumerism survey, 1976-1977 (Box 12)
    - Study--Business and consumerism survey, 1976-1977 (Box 45)
    - Wahington correspondent--Daniel Posin, 1967-1968 (Box 12)
    - Wahington correspondent--David Hemanway, 1968-1969; 2 folders (Box 12)
    - Wahington Office--David Swankin, 1969-1972; 2 folders (Box 13)
    - Wahington Office--Peter Schuck, 1972-1973; 2 folders (Box 13)
    - Wahington Office--Peter Schuck, 1972-1973 (Box 45)
  - Donal Dinwiddie--Source Material Files, 1952-1977; 6
    - Advertising--Deceptive, 1963-1971 (Box 13)
    - Advertising substantiation, 1971-1972; 2 folders (Box 13)
    - Alcoholic beverages--Consumers Union testing, 1971-1972 (Box 13)
    - Auto copy--Experimental approach, 1971 (Box 13)
    - Breakfast cereals and nutrition, 1970-1971 (Box 13)
    - Breakfast cereals and nutrition, 1970-1971; 3 folders (Box 14)
    - Breakfast cereals and nutrition, 1970-1971; 2 folders (Box 45)
    - Chloromycetin (antibiotic), 1971 (Box 14)
    - College education costs, 1960-1968; 3 folders (Box 14)
    - Corvair evaluation, 1965-1973 (Box 14)
    - Federal Housing Administration, 1962 (Box 14)
    - Flammable fabrics, 1972 (Box 14)
    - Fluoridation, 1968-1971 (Box 14)
    - Fluoridation, 1968-1971 (Box 15)
    - Food, 1964-1967; 4 folders (Box 15)
    - Food and drug laws, 1960-1968 (Box 15)
    - Food and drug laws, 1960-1968 (Box 45)
    - Food prices, 1966-1968 (Box 15)
    - Freedom of Information Act, 1969-1970 (Box 15)
    - Freedom of Information Act, 1969-1970 (Box 45)
    - Frauds--Health clubs, 1959-1962 (Box 15)
    - Frauds--Home improvement, 1952-1968 (Box 15)
    - Furniture, 1959-1967 (Box 16)
    - Galbraith, John Kenneth, 1967 (Box 16)
    - Galbraith, John Kenneth, 1967 (Box 48)
    - Gasoline and oil; pipeline industry, 1966-1968 (Box 16)
    - Good Housekeeping Seal of Approval, 1968-1969 (Box 16)
    - Grass roots organizing, 1959-1964; 3 folders (Box 16)
    - Grass roots organizing, 1959-1964 (Box 45)
    - Greening of America, 1970 (Box 16)
    - Guarantees, 1958-1967 (Box 16)
    - Headaches, 1970 (Box 16)
    - Headaches, 1970 (Box 45)
    - Health care, 1967-1970 (Box 16)
    - Health education in the schools, 1967 (Box 16)
    - Health insurance, 1969-1970 (Box 16)
    - Health insurance, 1969-1970 (Box 17)
    - Hearing aids (VA case), 1965-1969 (Box 17)
    - Hurrahs (praise and compliments), 1967-1972 (Box 17)
    - Insurance, auto, 1967-1970; 5 folders (Box 17)
    - Insurance, auto, 1967-1970 (Box 45)
    - Investments, 1966-1977 (Box 17)
    - Jewelry, 1963 (Box 17)
    - Lobbyists, 1965 (Box 18)
    - Medical research, 1965-1970 (Box 18)
    - Medicare, 1966-1967 (Box 18)
    - Medicare, 1966-1967 (Box 45)
    - Metric system, 1968 (Box 18)
    - Microwave ovens, 1972-1973 (Box 18)
    - National Commission on Food Marketing, 1965 (Box 18)
    - Oil shale, 1967 (Box 18)
    - Overweight/Obesity, 1969 (Box 18)
    - Packaging, 1965-1966 (Box 18)
    - Paser Magnum (anti-pollution automotive accessory), 1971-1972 (Box 18)
    - Patents, 1963-1965 (Box 18)
    - Pesticides, 1963-1969 (Box 18)
    - Porter, Sylvia (economist and journalist), 1960-1961 (Box 18)
    - Poverty, 1965-1972 (Box 18)
    - Poverty, 1965-1972 (Box 45)
    - Quackery, 1963-1967 (Box 18)
    - Shell No-Pest Strip, 1970-1972 (Box 18)
    - STP oil additive, 1970-1973 (Box 18)
    - Telephone rates, 1966-1967 (Box 19)
    - Television commercials, 1959-1967 (Box 19)
    - Tobacco, 1967-1968 (Box 19)
    - Toys, 1971-1972 (Box 19)
    - Toys, 1972 (Box 45)
    - Truth-in-Lending, 1966-1967 (Box 19)
    - Truth-in-Lending, 1967 (Box 45)
    - Vitamin C and the common cold, 1970-1971 (Box 19)
    - Wards Auto World articles, 1971 (Box 19)
    - Warranties, 1964-1968 (Box 19)
    - Water pollution, 1965-1967; 2 folders (Box 19)
    - Water pollution, 1965-1967; 2 folders (Box 45)
    - Weights and measures, 1964-1965; 2 folders (Box 19)
    - X-ray radiation, 1967-1968; 2 folders (Box 20)
    - Youth market, 1967-1969 (Box 20)
    - Youth market, 1967-1969 (Box 48)
    - Youth movement, 1967-1969 (Box 20)
  - Guy Henle (Managing Editor, 1973-1984), 1973-1975; 7
    - Correspondence and memoranda, 1973-1975 (Box 20)
  - Harold Field (Executive Editor), 1958; 8
    - Correspondence and memoranda, 1958 (Box 20)
  - Howard Allaway (Managing Editor), 1963; 9
    - Correspondence and memoranda, 1963 (Box 20)
  - Irwin Landau--Correspondence, 1968-1989; 10
    - General, 1968-1971 (Box 20)
    - Gil Thelan (Washington editorial office), 1972-1977; 2 folders (Box 20)
    - Interoffice memos, 1973-1974 (Box 20)
    - Letters from Landau, 1973-1986; 6 folders (Box 21)
    - Letters from Landau, 1986-1989; 3 folders (Box 22)
    - Letters from Landau and Rhoda Karpatkin, 1975-1988; 2 folders (Box 22)
    - Letters from Landau to Walker Sanbach on Editor's position, 1973 (Box 22)
    - Memos to Editorial staff, 1970-1975 (Box 22)
    - Operations Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 22)
    - Production memos, 1974-1978 (Box 22)
    - Washington Office, 1973-1974 (Box 22)
    - Washington Office, 1974-1977 (Box 23)
  - Irwin Landau--Subject Files, 1968-1988; 11
    - Advertising column, 1974-1976 (Box 23)
    - Advertising in and of Consumer Reports, 1974-1978 (Box 23)
    - Auto rentals, 1974 (Box 23)
    - Banking, 1973-1975 (Box 23)
    - Better Business Bureau, 1974-1975 (Box 23)
    - Cable Television, 1973 (Box 23)
    - Chrysler--Omni/Horizon, 1978-1979 (Box 23)
    - Consultants, 1973-1974; 2 folders (Box 23)
    - Coverage in Consumer Reports, 1973-1974 (Box 24)
    - Drinking water series, 1973-1975; 3 folders (Box 24)
    - Editorial staff, 1968-1975 (Box 24)
    - Home buying services (Merle Dowd), 1972-1974 (Box 24)
    - Household movers article--Criticism, 1975 (Box 24)
    - Insurance series, 1973-1977 (Box 24)
    - Interview with Jim Galloway, 1974 (Box 24)
    - Laetrile article--Criticism, 1977-1978 (Box 24)
    - Landlord-tenant relations article, 1974 (Box 25)
    - Legal services, 1973-1975 (Box 25)
    - Letter to President Bush, in Consumer Reports, 1988 (Box 25)
    - Media and the Consumer (Frank Pollock), 1973-1975 (Box 25)
    - Medical malpractice article, 1973-1978 (Box 25)
    - Meetings, speeches, public appearances, etc., 1974-1982 (Box 25)
    - Memo to members, 1973 (Box 25)
    - Milk article, 1973 (Box 25)
    - Policy statements, 1973-1979; 2 folders (Box 25)
    - Policy on chemicals, 1978 (Box 26)
    - Promotion of Consumer Reports, 1975-1977 (Box 26)
    - Publishing program, 1984 (Box 26)
    - Ralph Nader, 1973-1975 (Box 26)
    - Record reviews, 1974-1982 (Box 26)
    - Record reviews--Consultant Martin Bookspan, 1977-1982 (Box 26)
    - Search committee for Executive Director, 1973 (Box 26)
    - Staff obituaries, 1973-1976 (Box 26)
    - Syndicated newspaper column, 1975-1976 (Box 26)
    - Union relations (Newspaper Guild), 1974-1981; 4 folders (Box 26)
    - Union relations (Newspaper Guild), 1978-1980 (Box 45)
    - Union relations (Newspaper Guild), 1982-1988; 4 folders (Box 27)
  - Jean Whitehill (Managing Editor), 1946-1950; 12
    - Correspondence and memoranda, 1946-1950 (Box 27)
  - Joel Gurin, 1996-1997; 13
    - Correspondence and memoranda, 1996-1997 (Box 27)
  - Labor Editors, 1936-1940; 14
    - Correspondence and memoranda, 1936-1940 (Box 27)
      Includes: Alexander Crosby, Jane Metzger, Lydia Altschuler, Mark Marvin
  - Mildred Brady, 1938-1965; 15
    - Allstate Insurance--Controversy on Consumer Reports articles, 1962 (Box 27)
    - Articles, 1956-1965 (Box 27)
    - Articles--Canned ham, 1962 (Box 27)
    - Biographical, personal, obituaries, 1965; 2 folders (Box 27)
    - Consultant agreement, 1960 (Box 27)
    - Correspondence, 1956-1960; 3 folders (Box 27)
    - Correspondence, 1960-1965; 11 folders (Box 28)
    - Correspondence--Colston Warne and other Board members, 1959-1965 (Box 28)
    - Correspondence--Inter-office, 1959-1964 (Box 28)
    - FHA Draper case, 1948-1954 (Box 28)
      Home improvement loan dispute involving allegations of forgery, the Federal Housing Authority, Bank of America, Enterprise Construction Company and Lillian Draper, an employee of Consumers Union.
    - Milk laws and regulation, 1944-1963 (Box 28)
    - Permissions to reprint Consumer Reports content, 1963-1964 (Box 28)
    - Speeches, 1953-1965 (Box 28)
    - Television panel--Does Advertising Deserve Its Reputation?, 1962 (Box 28)
    - Testimonies, 1955-1965; 2 folders (Box 29)
    - The Neutral Thousands, 1938 (Box 29)
      Known by the initials TNT, it was an anti-union organization led by one Bessie Ochs, a California activist, in 1937. It disbanded in 1940 upon investigation by the LaFollette Committee and the U.S. Justice Department. Source: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Neutral_Thousands
  - Patricia Jenkins (Managing Editor), 1963-1967; 16
    - Correspondence and memoranda, 1963-1967 (Box 29)
  - Paul Kellam (Managing Editor), 1972-1973; 17
    - Correspondence and memoranda, 1972-1973 (Box 29)
  - Robert Klein (Economics Editor), 1967-1972; 18
    - Correspondence and memoranda, 1967-1972 (Box 29)
    - Testimonies, 1969-1970 (Box 29)
- Publication Production Files, 1937-1994; 4
  - Special Publications, 1937-1975; 19
    - Buying Guide--Correspondence, 1950-1975; 2 folders (Box 30)
    - Buying Guide--Distribution and style notes, 1938 (Box 30)
    - Custom-Built Radio-Phonograph Instructions, 1948-1949 (Box 30)
    - Hooking Up Top-Rated Loudspeaker Systems, 1959 (Box 30)
    - How to Get Your Money's Worth, 1959 (Box 30)
    - Installation Notes for the Complete Stereo Record-Playing Systems, 1959 (Box 30)
    - Installing a Hi-Fi Turntable, 1959 (Box 30)
    - New Techniques of Consumer Deception in Weights and Measures, 1966 (Box 30)
    - Report on Two Leading Makes of "Custom-Built" Radio Receivers, 1937 (Box 30)
    - Student Edition, 1950-1963 (Box 30)
  - Source Materials, Proofs, etc., 1942-1994; 20
    Includes correspondence, letters from readers, subject files, drafts and proof copies of articles, booklets and other printed materials.
    - Advertising, 1942-1972; 2 folders (Box 30)
    - Advertising in Disguise, 1986 (Box 31)
    - Advertising in Disguise, 1986 (Box 45)
    - Advertising in Disguise, 1986; 2 folders (Box 48)
    - AIDS: Deadly but Hard to Contract, 1986; 4 folders (Box 31)
    - AIDS: Deadly but Hard to Contract, 1986 (Box 45)
    - AIDS: Deadly but Hard to Contract, 1986 (Box 48)
    - Alcoholism, 1966-1974; 2 folders (Box 31)
    - Antibiotics in Animal Feed, 1985 (Box 31)
    - Antibiotics in Animal Feed, 1985 (Box 46)
    - Antibiotics in Animal Feed, 1985 (Box 48)
    - Automobile safety, 1966 (Box 32)
    - Automobile safety, 1966; 2 folders (Box 46)
    - Automobile safety, 1966 (Box 48)
    - Bicycles--Frame testing--Drawings (From Westfield Manufacturing), 1944-1945 (Box 50)
    - Bicycles--Joint testing--Drawings (From Arnold Schwinn), 1946-1949 (Box 50)
    - Birth control, abortion, 1972; 2 folders (Box 32)
    - Birth control, abortion, 1972 (Box 46)
    - Birth control, contraceptives, 1954-1971; 3 folders (Box 32)
    - Birth control, contraceptives, 1970-1971 (Box 50)
    - Business Lobbying: Threat to the Consumer Interest, 1978; 2 folders (Box 32)
    - Business Lobbying: Threat to the Consumer Interest, 1978 (Box 46)
    - Business Lobbying: Threat to the Consumer Interest, 1978 (Box 48)
    - Cancer, 1950-1975; 2 folders (Box 33)
    - Cancer cures, fraudulent, 1949-1965 (Box 33)
    - Cancer cures, fraudulent, 1949-1965 (Box 46)
    - Case Against Oil and Steel Import Quotas, 1972 (Box 33)
    - Case Against Oil and Steel Import Quotas, 1972 (Box 46)
    - Children for the Childless (Infertility, artificial insemination), 1946-1959; 4 folders (Box 33)
    - Children for the Childless (Infertility, artificial insemination), 1946 (Box 46)
    - Children for the Childless (Infertility, artificial insemination), 1949-1959 (Box 34)
    - Chiropractors--Critical letters received regarding article, 1994; 6 folders (Box 34)
    - Chiropractors--Critical letters received regarding article, 1994; 2 folders (Box 35)
    - Chiropractors--Neutral letters received regarding article, 1994 (Box 35)
    - Chiropractors--Positive letters received regarding article, 1994 (Box 35)
    - Clorox Case (Bleach), 1967 (Box 35)
    - Clorox Case (Bleach), 1967 (Box 48)
    - Consumers and class action suits, 1970-1975 (Box 35)
    - Consumers and class action suits, 1970-1975 (Box 46)
    - Consumers Union's Omni/Horizon Report, 1978 (Box 35)
    - Credit Cards for Causes, 1988 (Box 35)
    - Credit Cards for Causes, 1988 (Box 46)
    - FDA Sniffs Out Vitamin Hype, 1988 (Box 35)
    - FDA Sniffs Out Vitamin Hype, 1988 (Box 46)
    - Fear of Fat: The Medical Evidence, 1985 (Box 35)
    - Fear of Fat: The Medical Evidence, 1985 (Box 36)
    - Fear of Fat: The Medical Evidence, 1985 (Box 46)
    - Fear of Fat: The Medical Evidence, 1985 (Box 48)
    - Foods, Drugs, or Frauds?, 1985; 5 folders (Box 36)
    - Foods, Drugs, or Frauds?, 1985 (Box 46)
    - Foods, Drugs, or Frauds?, 1985 (Box 48)
    - Ford's Better Idea: Collapsing Front Wheels, 1970 (Box 36)
    - Ford's Better Idea: Collapsing Front Wheels, 1970 (Box 37)
    - Fords in Reverse, 1985 (Box 37)
    - Fords in Reverse, 1985 (Box 46)
    - Fords in Reverse, 1985 (Box 49)
    - Forget About Cholesterol?, 1990; 3 folders (Box 37)
    - Forget About Cholesterol?, 1990 (Box 49)
    - Freedom of Information Act, 1967-1973; 2 folders (Box 37)
    - Freedom of Information Act, 1967-1973 (Box 46)
    - Government Regulation of Industry, 1950-1951 (Box 38)
    - How Import Quotas Raise Consumer Prices, 1969 (Box 38)
    - How Import Quotas Raise Consumer Prices, 1969 (Box 49)
    - How Remington Shaves the Truth, 1985 (Box 38)
    - How Remington Shaves the Truth, 1985 (Box 46)
    - How to Buy a Volvo at Mercedes Prices, 1988 (Box 38)
    - How to Buy a Volvo at Mercedes Prices, 1988 (Box 46)
    - How to Buy a Volvo at Mercedes Prices, 1988 (Box 49)
    - Immune Power Diet, 1986 (Box 38)
    - Immune Power Diet, 1986 (Box 46)
    - Immune Power Diet, 1986 (Box 49)
    - Indoor Air Pollution, 1985; 4 folders (Box 38)
    - Indoor Air Pollution, 1985 (Box 46)
    - Indoor Air Pollution, 1985 (Box 49)
    - Is a Mastectomy Necessary?, 1988 (Box 38)
    - Is a Mastectomy Necessary?, 1988 (Box 39)
    - Is a Mastectomy Necessary?, 1988 (Box 49)
    - Latest on Diet and Your Heart, 1985 (Box 39)
    - Latest on Diet and Your Heart, 1985 (Box 46)
    - Latest on Diet and Your Heart, 1985 (Box 49)
    - Living Off the Fat of the Sea (Seafood and diet), 1986; 2 folders (Box 39)
    - Living Off the Fat of the Sea (Seafood and diet), 1986 (Box 46)
    - Man Bites Ford, 1970 (Box 46)
    - Medicine--Quackery, 1970-1971 (Box 39)
    - Memo to Members, 1988 (Box 39)
    - Memo to Members, 1988 (Box 46)
    - Memo to Members, 1988 (Box 49)
    - Mercury Scare (Dentistry), 1986 (Box 39)
    - Mercury Scare (Dentistry), 1986; 4 folders (Box 40)
    - Mercury Scare (Dentistry), 1986; 2 folders (Box 47)
    - Mercury Scare (Dentistry), 1986 (Box 49)
    - Nursing homes, 1963-1966; 3 folders (Box 40)
    - Nursing homes, 1964 (Box 41)
    - Nursing homes, 1964 (Box 47)
    - Pesticide Increases Cancer Risk, 1988 (Box 41)
    - Pesticide Increases Cancer Risk, 1988 (Box 47)
    - Product safety, 1969-1975 (Box 41)
    - Public Utilities--Gas and Electric, 1942-1975; 2 folders (Box 41)
    - Radiation, 1968-1974 (Box 41)
    - Salt and High Blood Pressure, 1984; 3 folders (Box 42)
    - Salt and High Blood Pressure, 1984 (Box 47)